Set targets to Sato and Jin...
Engage Visualization Right!
I found you...Sato and Jin!
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
No!
This way!
Dammit! How did he find us?
Gotta be the Visualization Right...
Warning
Those in pursuit of other
participants within the
Designated Area must
disengage within 10 seconds
and move to Nerima Ward.
Those in pursuit of other
participants within the
Designated Area must
disengage within 10 seconds
and move to Nerima Ward.
Those in pursuit of other
participants within the
Designated Area must
disengage within 10 seconds
and move to Nerima Ward.
Failure to comply for any reason
will result in immediate execution.
Warning
Those in pursuit of
other participants
within the Designated Area
must disengage within
10 seconds and move
to Nerima Ward.
Failure to comply for any
reason will result in
immediate execution.
Begin moving to Nerima Ward
within ten seconds...?
"Immediate execution"?!
Warning
Those in pursuit of other
participants within the
Designated Area must
disengage within 10 seconds
and move to Nerima Ward.
Those in pursuit of other
participants within the
Designated Area must
disengage within 10 seconds
and move to Nerima Ward.
Those in pursuit of other
participants within the
Designated Area must
disengage within 10 seconds
and move to Nerima Ward.
Failure to comply for any reason
will result in immediate execution.
What's going on?
D-Damn...!
Hey, he went away...
Y-Ya mean we're safe...?
Control Room
He-he-he...
Found me a couple of suckers!
Reminds me of summer bugs
flying towards the light, for real!
It's game over for you two dimwits!
Wh-Who the heck are you?!
Don't expect him to answer that...
My name, you ask?
Or maybe not...
Messenger of the Netherworlds!
Borinmaru Gokokuhotenji!
Borinmaru Gokokuhotenji
Wh-What a long name...
I bet you're scared
outta your wits, for real!
Should we run for it?
Let's try to keep the peace and talk it out.
Mm-yup.
Umm... Go... Gokoku... Go? Gogoho?
Gokokuhojo-san!
That just means "plentiful
harvest" in Japanese!
You're way off, Omi!
Gogo... Bori... Go... Go... Gobo!
Stop listing off Japanese vegetables!
We don't mean any harm!
Mm-yup!
Trust us!
Gobo!
So you're both set on "Gobo"...
Dammit!
I'll make you both rust on my ruler...
Rust... on a ruler...?
Do plastic rulers even rust?
Wait, what?
Wow, dude
Hmph... Sure it does!
With my Right that carves
everything in its path...
The Zantetsu Right!
Zantetsu Right
Zantetsu Right...?
Which means you two suckers are
new toys to take my frustrations out on!
If you don't wanna die, swear
that you'll become my servants!
I'll kill you here and now
if you refuse, for real!
I refuse!
O-O-Omi?! That was quick.
You little...
Huh?
What happened? I was gonna
persuade them but nothing came out...
Maybe I'm a little nervous. Oh, well...
I'll just go ahead and get it over with!
No!
...Huh?
Wait...
Hey! You there, pea size!
You're being called a pea by a root veg!
Why aren't ya scared?
Cause there's no such thing
as a Zantetsu Right.
Zantetsu Right
Man, is he one of those know-it-alls?!
I-I dunno, are you sure about that?!
There could be one!
Maybe you just don't know about it!
There's no chance it exists.
Really?
How could a Right "carve everything"?
The name doesn't fit the ability.
This is bad...
Besides, Rights don't give explanations.
There's no way to know that.
This is really bad...
I don't get it, but he's for real real.
Well, um...
I'm sorry! I was just showing off!
You sure are quick to apologize!
But you sure seem to know a lot...
Come on, spill the deets! For real!
Did you forget what you said
literally five seconds ago?!
Whaddaya think? Can we trust him?
I wouldn't trust anyone in this situation
after just a few minutes, but...
Since he knows about Rights, he could
have some kind of Right or Prime Right...
We can talk to him a bit and see.
Control Room
Oh... That's unfortunate, for real.
Alright, now your turn, Gobo.
Don't settle on "Gobo"!
I'm from class-2 at Itabashi Chuo
Middle School! Borinmaru Gokokuhotenji!
He didn't miss a beat!
My family and friends all died during
the test run, and I was all alone.
I was so sad and scared of dying that I shut
myself in my house until Tasuketsu started.
But on Day One, I found myself headed
to the Designated Area of Suginami Ward.
But what I saw made me lose hope...
Something that couldn't possibly exist.
It was a dragon, I'm sure of it.
I took off and ran for my life
when I found an envelope of Rights.
That's the only success I've had so far.
Other than that, I've been cooped up here.
A dragon... No doubt it's under
the Production Attribute.
Gotta be the baldie macho dude with Sensei.
I'm pretty good with machines.
So I tweaked all the security
cameras in this area
and sent the footage to this Control Room.
I've been watching for
passersby every day since.
I thought I could bluff some chumps
into finding postboxes for me.
You mean we were those chumps?
Correct!
So I sent off the weird guy
that was chasing you
and chose you two since
you were closer to my age.
Hey, that reminds me.
Why did Sensei run off?
Right of
Presentation
The Right of Presentation!
I displayed a message in a show
window where he was running.
Warning
Those in pursuit of other
participants within the
Designated Area must
disengage within 10 seconds
and move to Nerima Ward.
Those in pursuit of other
participants within the
Designated Area must
disengage within 10 seconds
and move to Nerima Ward.
Those in pursuit of other
participants within the
Designated Area must
disengage within 10 seconds
and move to Nerima Ward.
Failure to comply for any reason
will result in immediate execution.
Warning
Those in pursuit of
other participants
within the Designated Area
must disengage within
10 seconds and move
to Nerima Ward.
Failure to comply for any
reason will result in
immediate execution.
Gave him orders to head to Nerima
or be executed immediately
with the Emperor's emblem.
Warning
Those in pursuit of other
participants within the
Designated Area must
disengage within 10 seconds
and move to Nerima Ward.
Those in pursuit of other
participants within the
Designated Area must
disengage within 10 seconds
and move to Nerima Ward.
Those in pursuit of other
participants within the
Designated Area must
disengage within 10 seconds
and move to Nerima Ward.
Failure to comply for any reason
will result in immediate execution.
That'll do the trick...
Prime Rights: 12 left
Rights: 45 left
40 years of age
Under or Over
1,081,990 people left
You've seen the Tasuketsu screen with the
remaining number of Rights and people, right?
That was all me, you know.
Seriously?! That's crazy!
I'm surprised at sumthin' else...
What's that?
Why are you two being
so honest about this stuff?
I-I never said I was telling the truth!
Same here, I was just lying!
Eh?!
Shaddup!
Screw you, Antenna Head!
I knew it, they're both idiots.
And they're both telling the truth...
You want me to display your
personal information across town?!
Why don't you get kicked in the ass
by Saneatsu, you dummy!
Too bad for you I'm from Itabashi
He seems like a good guy.
where we have awesome defense
from the natural landscape!
And his Presentation Right
will probably come in handy...
I hope your nails rot, you idiot!
If I could just introduce him to
Saneatsu, he'd know what to do.
You literally make no sense, idiot!
But the problem is how
to meet up with them...
Gobo!
Don't call me by that name, for real!
Do you wanna help us defeat the Emperor?
L-Like I'd do something that scary...
So what? You gonna stay here
forever until you die?
You guys are something else...
With everyone dead,
I barely feel alive myself.
And yet you're so calm. Talking 'bout
defeating the Emperor and stuff...
I'm not cut out for that.
I gave up, lashed out, and still
barely function as normal.
We aren't so different. If it weren't
for the Pres we'd still be in a panic...
It was mostly luck.
I found myself in a group with some
brave people that were willing to fight.
That's how I feel, at least.
I know I'm not alone!
Having strong teammates makes me
stronger, too. I can still laugh and fight.
Sure, it may not matter
if we fight or hide in the end.
It makes no difference
if we can't submit a question.
99.9% of this comes down to luck.
But there's zero chance if you give up!
Only those who try to survive
can choose their own fate!
Isn't that what life's all about?
Sato-kun...
That said, I'm not very smart, so I have
no clue if anything I say is right, but...
No, you're right...
Worst-case scenario, you die
without doing anything...
Best-case scenario, you live
by accomplishing something...!
I'll bet my life on the best outcome, too!
So? How do we meet up
with your group, like, for real?
We're supposed to meet up at the
North Exit of Narimasu Station, but...
What do you think?
Let's see... Ummm...
I'm not that smart, either, you know...
Sato-kun, do you have any nicknames?
Sure, why?
Perfect. I have an idea.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Narita-kun, should we wait
for Sato-kun and Jin-kun?
I'll wait for them till morning,
even if it's by myself.
This is the last time and place
we agreed to meet,
and we have no way of contacting each other.
If we can't meet up here, we might never...
No way! It's not time yet, is it?
No, it's still 23:55.
What's going on?
Tomorrow A Ippy-hiko HBD day, ya mean.
My seedy haul!
What is this...?
This is... a message of some kind.
Narita-kun, can you decode this by chance?
Omi and Kazuhiko are safe...!
What?! Where does it say that?
It's pretty risky, but...
This way, no one else will
fully understand what it means.
So it was Kazuhiko's idea?
Nah, he couldn't do this.
It was probably Omi.
What does it say?
"Ippy-hiko" is Kazuhiko's nickname.
Hey! I was the one that started that!
Tomorrow A Ippy-hiko HBD day, ya mean.
My seedy haul!
"Ya mean" is Omi's phrase.
Assuming it's a message to meet up...
"Tomorrow" refers to the date,
and "A" is code for "AM".
Tomorrow A Ippy-hiko HBD day, ya mean.
"HBD" is about Kazuhiko's
birthday, April 28th.
So why write "day" in English?
They probably want to
emphasize the date, the 28th.
But "28AM" makes no sense.
Right, so add the two figures.
"2" and "8" make...
Of course! 10 AM!
What about "My seedy haul"?
Never mind! I got it after saying it aloud.
City Hall of the Designated Area.
You understood all that?
This isn't too difficult to make out.
Omi must've made sure I could decode it.
But the key word is "my".
This has to mean something...
My seedy haul!
His own city hall? Like the nearest
one by the karaoke place?
Nah, I think this is "mai"
meaning "every" in Japanese.
How does that make sense?
Tomorrow A Ippy-hiko HBD day, ya mean.
My seedy haul!
Others might be able to decode "city hall"...
They included a Plan B in case
something happens and we can't meet up.
I see. So every day at 10:00AM
starting tomorrow...
They'll be at City Hall
in whatever Designated Area.
Not bad, Jin-kun.
But how were they able to
display this screen?
They must have gained a Right
or Prime Right to display messages.
Makes sense...
Tomorrow A Ippy-hiko HBD day, ya mean.
My seedy haul!
You must be relieved, Saneatsu.
Yeah...
Cut it out with that face
before I break your neck!
It's time.
We will...
not be taking tally.
Huh? What's happening?
A-Are we safe?! Is it over?!
Hang on!
Starting tomorrow at 12:00AM,
Tasuketsu will move on to Stage Two.
Stage Two...?
Some rules are subject to change.
Questions will only be
accepted through red laptops.
Tallies will not take place
until a question is accepted.
Laptops will have a remaining
battery life of roughly one hour.
They may be charged, but please note that
AC adapters are placed in a different location.
Laptops will be collected
every day at 23:55PM.
Identify and enter passwords
located within Designated Areas
to extend the collection
deadline for 24 hours.
Doesn't this mean we're in for
a fight over these laptops?
Yeah. We're in trouble.
Laptops can be carried
beyond Designated Areas.
People will start coming out of hiding...
especially owners of
advantageous Prime Rights.
But we gotta keep going!
Let's do it, everyone!
This stage transition...
Was it the plan all along?
Or was it...
Woah, who knew these postboxes
vanish into thin air!
Stage transition, huh?
Not bad, considering they
only had three minutes...
The Emperor sure is fickle, changing the rules
because of one measly submission.
However...
None of these halfwits stand
a chance against them.
I'll burn down any filth that gets in my way.
This means war. I'll blow
the entire human race to bits.
Kita Ward City Hall
Omi! Kazuhiko!
Saneatsu!
We did it! You really came!
Great job, Omi!
I'm glad you got it!
Sup, Ippy-hiko!
Huh? What?! Ryuta!
Wait, weren't you...?
Dead? I thought so, too.
I willed myself back to life, I guess!
That's awesome! Man, I'm so happy!
"That's awesome"? He really is an idiot...
Seriously?
Where's everyone else?
Saaya and Eren Senpai are both safe.
We've met up with the Pres, too.
Ya mean he really did come back ta life!
Yup! Along with Ryuta!
Back ta life...
Look at y'all!
You sure flock in a big group!
Who's that?
Wanna beat him up?
Eh?
Wait, wait! Hold up! He's with us, our team!
Our message last night and the remaining
count on the Tasuketsu screen
are all thanks to his Presentation Right.
Oh, right... Great, umm...
Hmph... Fine.
I'll enlighten you with my name.
Rahatzel Gokokuhotenji De La Mori Ogai
Masamune El Borinmaru of the Darkness...
...Come again?
A.K.A. Gobo.
I like that.
Why...
Where's everyone else?
Saaya and Eren Senpai are on standby
somewhere else so they wouldn't be in danger.
In danger?
Your message. I'm guessing
others have figured it out, too.
The only information they wouldn't know
is Kazuhiko's birthday, so the time.
Which means the longer we're here,
the more dangerous it is.
We'll meet up with the President first.
He's patrolling the area just outside.
Let's go!
They're actually cool... for real!
Kita Ward City Hall
We'll take a detour to meet with the Pres.
Let's think of a strategy
to find laptops after that.
Ryuta?
Hey, don't run off!
Thank God I finally found you guys!
I've been wanting to talk,
so I was looking for you.
Let's all get along
like the classmates we are!
That's...
The guy from the first day of the test run...
The second year who went
missing the next day...
I believed you'd all still be alive!
Good thing I came, just in case.
Um... Senpai...
Hey! You remembered me?
Why did you disappear?
Oh, right... that...
How about I answer
if you tell me your motive?
Our motive?
You haven't given up on Tasuketsu, have you?
We're defeating the Emperor
and putting an end to Tasuketsu!
I know it sounds crazy! But—
I guess we're the same, then!
You know, I lost everything that day...
So I said "screw it" and ran off,
but... I couldn't do anything alone.
I've been trying to find my way
back to you guys ever since.
So that's what happened...
Something's wrong here.
I have an eerie feeling,
like something rotten's in the air.
My instincts are telling me
not to trust this guy.
Can I join you all in your fight?
I'm sure everyone will be
happy you're joining us!
Welcome, Iruga Senpai!
Mido and Ren Iruga. Those two are dangerous.
Someone has to stop them.
I recognize that look...
How did you find out?
Jeez, calm down, will ya?
How rude, trying to chop off my head
out of nowhere like that!
What the hell did he do?!
Was that a Prime Right?
Come on, let's all be civil.
If I wanted to kill you, I would've done it
already... like when we shook hands.
What do you want?
I just want the kid with the Rejection Right.
Omi?!
You guys are practically wasting his talent.
What do you want Omi for?!
To defeat the Emperor.
Go ahead and decline if you're not up for it.
It's not like I'm the one who wants him.
It's Mido, isn't it?!
So you do know!
That's right! It's that creepy piece of shit.
Wait, do you even know what Mido looks like?
I guess that Isshiki lady
didn't end up specifying...
"End up"? What did you do to her?!
Huh? I killed her.
Why the long face?
Is it bad that I killed someone?
O-Of course it's ba—
Just what do you plan on doing
when you find the Emperor?
Aren't you gonna kill them?
You cold-blooded murderer!
Submitting a question in Tasuketsu
is no different. It's murder.
You're killing people based on
some preconceived logic.
Don't tell me you believe in justice...
I'd laugh my ass off.
I haven't submitted anything yet!
But you're looking for
those laptops, aren't you?
You'll submit something
when you find one, right?
You said defeating the Emperor
would be murder...
So the Emperor is human, then?
Yeah, it's a person. Not that
I know anything about them.
Huh... The Rejection Right kid
hasn't told you anything, then?
What's this got to do with Omi?
My, my... You don't even know that part?
It's cause we're from the same camp, duh!
Camp...?
Transition